

Graphic Design + Marketing Specialist

Jenna Howard

- j.m.howard30@gmail.com
- Macon, GA
- jhoward.design
- **%** (478) 719-0474

Profile

With 10 years in digital & traditional design, I specialize in turning ideas into powerful visual content. My expertise includes brand awareness, visual storytelling, graphic design, & client engagement. I've served a range of clients, ensuring each brand's voice resonates with their target.

Skills

- O LinkedIn
- FIGMA
- MailChimp
- Adobe Photoshop
- Facebook
- Adobe Illustrator
- Google Ads + Analytics
- Adobe PremierePro

Employment

2020 - now Marketing Specialist at SPINEN

Collaborated with internal and client teams to craft visual assets for social media platforms. Orchestrated targeted digital ad campaigns that garnered over 30,000 impressions alongside email marketing initiatives that generated in excess of \$30,000 in revenue. Designed sales materials & internal training tools as well.

2019 - now Freelance Graphic Designer

Overhauled client branding & content planning across digital platforms including social media & Google Business. Developed & maintained client websites. Started mailing list for customer newsletters. Produced brochures, menus, photo shoots, signage, & content. Reported & presented client analytics.

2018 - 2019 Project Manager at Third Wave Digital

Administered projects for national & small business campaigns. Executed complex digital communications on behalf of key clients (e.g. 7-Eleven) including 3rd party vendors. Maintained a visual matrix of both content & format variations for menu boards across region, store types, & times of day for >200 stores.

Education

2011 - 2015 Georgia College & State University

Bachelor of Arts in Mass Communication